### **Profile**

I am a Flutter developer and UI Designer. I started to develop in 2019 during my preparatory course in the Federal University of Ceará. I believe that development is more than delivering a software. Being a dev is about successfully solvin the user's problem, with the best design choices, best coding practices and the best experience that you can purpose.

### **Education**

#### Federal University of Ceará

Coding: Programming Preparatory Course 02/2019 - 12/2019.

# State School of Professional Education Juarez Távora

Technical Highschool in Computer Networks. 01/2019 - 01/2022.

#### Startto.dev

Android/iOS/Web Apps creation with Flutter. 09/2022 - 06/2023.

#### CursoEmVideo

Git and Github course. 06/2020 - 07/2020.

## **Languages**

**Portuguese**, Native C2. **English**, Advanced C1. **German**, Basic A1.

# **Professional experience**

# Tech lead, Flutter frontend developer and UI Designer

Company: E-SPACE (MG, Brasil).

06/2023 - current.

#### Flutter frontend developer

Company: Athletic Gear (MG, Brasil). 07/2023 - 10/2024.

#### Freelance in Flutter frontend developer

Company: Polygonus (MG, Brasil). 01/2023 - 04/2023.

#### Trainee in Flutter development

Company: G4Flex Business and Services (CE, Brasil).

01/2022 - 06/2022.

## **Honors and awards**

Third Place Winner in IV Hackaton of Feira do Conhecimento, developed by Secretary of Science, Technology and College Education of the State of Ceará. News link

# **Projects**

#### **Portfolio Vinidev**

"If you are looking for someone who could bring your ideas and concepts to the fingertips of users with maestry in Flutter, clean code and best user experience as possible, you found it!". Responsive Portfolio web, developed with flutter.

Repository link

#### **Protechtor Gears**

Check a list of passwords, which comes directly from an API, with the user being able to add, read, edit and delete passwords. It is the result of a challenge for a Junior Flutter Developer Vacancy, which I was successful in passing.

Repository link

#### **BMI Check**

Calculate your BMI and discover if you are in your ideal body mass index and what is your body weight in a custom text with Health recommendations, and share with in social media. You can also change settings, theme and language.

Repository link

# **Technical skills**

- State management with Change/ValueNotifier, BLoC, Mobx and Triple package.
- MVC and Modular project pattern.
- Dependencies Injection with Provider, Injector and Modular package.
- Navigation with named routes of Material and Modular package.
- Rest APIs with dio and http packages.
- Local data persistence with hive and shared preferences packages.
- Themes implementation and themes changing with Material 3.
- RegEx for validations.
- · Unit Tests writing.
- Handlind exceptions with dartz library.
- Internationalization with flutter\_localiztions.
- Responsive applications.
- User Interface design.
- Clean code and clean architecture.